export const data = [
  {
    question: "In what year did The Rolling Stones release Exile on Main St.?",
    option1: "1978",
    option2: "1977",
    option3: "1972",
    option4: "1973",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which band released the album Nevermind?",
    option1: "Pearl Jam",
    option2: "Nirvana",
    option3: "Soundgarden",
    option4: "Foo Fighters",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the lead guitarist of Guns N' Roses during Appetite for Destruction?",
    option1: "Izzy Stradlin",
    option2: "Duff McKagan",
    option3: "Slash",
    option4: "Axl Rose",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which Beatles album features the song Eleanor Rigby?",
    option1: "Revolver",
    option2: "Rubber Soul",
    option3: "Help!",
    option4: "Abbey Road",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Pink Floyd’s The Wall was released in which year?",
    option1: "1979",
    option2: "1975",
    option3: "1980",
    option4: "1977",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which Oasis song begins with the lyrics 'Today is gonna be the day...'? ",
    option1: "Don't Look Back in Anger",
    option2: "Live Forever",
    option3: "Wonderwall",
    option4: "Champagne Supernova",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Aerosmith’s debut self-titled album was released in which year?",
    option1: "1970",
    option2: "1973",
    option3: "1975",
    option4: "1972",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the frontman of Soundgarden?",
    option1: "Eddie Vedder",
    option2: "Layne Staley",
    option3: "Chris Cornell",
    option4: "Kurt Cobain",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "KISS is best known for which of these stage trademarks?",
    option1: "Laser Harps",
    option2: "Face Paint and Pyrotechnics",
    option3: "Silent Performances",
    option4: "Acoustic-only Shows",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which Foo Fighters song was dedicated to Kurt Cobain?",
    option1: "My Hero",
    option2: "Everlong",
    option3: "Big Me",
    option4: "I'll Stick Around",
    ans: 4,
  },
];
